{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"TV Mounting Services","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/46380/":{"taskOID":46380,"originalTaskOID":46380,"setID":1305,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":6375,"questionDisplayText":"Type of mount","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of mount would you like?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8615,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Standard Fixed Mount","answerDisplayText":"Standard Fixed Mount","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8616,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Tilt mount","answerDisplayText":"Tilt mount","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8617,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Articulating (pivot) mount","answerDisplayText":"Articulating (pivot) mount","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8618,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"In wall recessed mount","answerDisplayText":"In wall recessed mount","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8619,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Not sure","answerDisplayText":"Not sure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6376,"questionDisplayText":"Surface","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the surface the TV will be mounted on?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8620,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Drywall","answerDisplayText":"Drywall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8621,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Plaster","answerDisplayText":"Plaster","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8623,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8622,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Stone or brick","answerDisplayText":"Stone or brick","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6377,"questionDisplayText":"Special Features","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of special features are you interested in?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8624,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Surge protection","answerDisplayText":"Surge protection","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8625,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Remote storage of electronics","answerDisplayText":"Remote storage of electronics","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8626,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Remote control articulating mount","answerDisplayText":"Remote control articulating mount","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8627,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Custom trim","answerDisplayText":"Custom trim","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8628,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"High end cabling","answerDisplayText":"High end cabling","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8629,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other features","answerDisplayText":"Other features","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6378,"questionDisplayText":"Wall and ceiling access","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Please describe the wall and ceiling access.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8630,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Walls must be left intact","answerDisplayText":"Walls must be left intact","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8631,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Partial wall access","answerDisplayText":"Partial wall access","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8632,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Attic or below floor access","answerDisplayText":"Attic or below floor access","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8633,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"All walls will be exposed","answerDisplayText":"All walls will be exposed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":10020,"questionDisplayText":"Request is for Commercial Location","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a commercial location?","shortQuestionText":"Is this a commercial location?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":6375,"questionDisplayText":"Type of mount","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of mount would you like?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8615,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Standard Fixed Mount","answerDisplayText":"Standard Fixed Mount","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8616,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Tilt mount","answerDisplayText":"Tilt mount","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8617,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Articulating (pivot) mount","answerDisplayText":"Articulating (pivot) mount","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8618,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"In wall recessed mount","answerDisplayText":"In wall recessed mount","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8619,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Not sure","answerDisplayText":"Not sure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":8615,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Standard Fixed Mount","answerDisplayText":"Standard Fixed Mount","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8616,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Tilt mount","answerDisplayText":"Tilt mount","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8617,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Articulating (pivot) mount","answerDisplayText":"Articulating (pivot) mount","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8618,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"In wall recessed mount","answerDisplayText":"In wall recessed mount","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8619,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Not sure","answerDisplayText":"Not sure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6376,"questionDisplayText":"Surface","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the surface the TV will be mounted on?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8620,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Drywall","answerDisplayText":"Drywall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8621,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Plaster","answerDisplayText":"Plaster","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8623,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8622,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Stone or brick","answerDisplayText":"Stone or brick","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":8620,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Drywall","answerDisplayText":"Drywall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8621,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Plaster","answerDisplayText":"Plaster","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8623,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8622,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Stone or brick","answerDisplayText":"Stone or brick","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6377,"questionDisplayText":"Special Features","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of special features are you interested in?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8624,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Surge protection","answerDisplayText":"Surge protection","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8625,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Remote storage of electronics","answerDisplayText":"Remote storage of electronics","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8626,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Remote control articulating mount","answerDisplayText":"Remote control articulating mount","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8627,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Custom trim","answerDisplayText":"Custom trim","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8628,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"High end cabling","answerDisplayText":"High end cabling","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8629,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other features","answerDisplayText":"Other features","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":8624,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Surge protection","answerDisplayText":"Surge protection","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8625,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Remote storage of electronics","answerDisplayText":"Remote storage of electronics","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8626,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Remote control articulating mount","answerDisplayText":"Remote control articulating mount","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8627,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Custom trim","answerDisplayText":"Custom trim","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8628,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"High end cabling","answerDisplayText":"High end cabling","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8629,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other features","answerDisplayText":"Other features","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6378,"questionDisplayText":"Wall and ceiling access","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Please describe the wall and ceiling access.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8630,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Walls must be left intact","answerDisplayText":"Walls must be left intact","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8631,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Partial wall access","answerDisplayText":"Partial wall access","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8632,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Attic or below floor access","answerDisplayText":"Attic or below floor access","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8633,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"All walls will be exposed","answerDisplayText":"All walls will be exposed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":8630,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Walls must be left intact","answerDisplayText":"Walls must be left intact","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8631,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Partial wall access","answerDisplayText":"Partial wall access","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8632,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Attic or below floor access","answerDisplayText":"Attic or below floor access","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8633,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"All walls will be exposed","answerDisplayText":"All walls will be exposed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":10020,"questionDisplayText":"Request is for Commercial Location","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a commercial location?","shortQuestionText":"Is this a commercial location?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/46380/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":46380,"taskName":"TV Wall Mount","taskDescription":"Mount TV on Wall","xmTaskDescriptor":"TV Mounting Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":80,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"TV flat articulating cantilever brackets","textMessagingName":"TV Mount","rolloverLongDesc":"Mounts TV to Wall.  Services can include routing and concealing power and audio/video cabling.","rolloverShortDesc":"Mount TVs on walls.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Wall Mount a TV.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"\u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e TV Installation | \u003ccity\u003e Television Wall Mount Installation","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":6,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":4,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"TV Mount","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"TV Wall Mount","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Home Theater Project","urlName":"TV-Wall-Mount","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best TV Installation \u0026 Mounting Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Costs \u0026 Reviews","searchKeywords":"TV,flat,articulating,cantilever,brackets,mounting,tilting,installations,Wall,Mount","emcCategoryOid":-12006,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":1305,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}